class QuestionModel {
  final String question;
  final List<String> option;
  final int correctAnswerIndex;

  const QuestionModel({
    required this.correctAnswerIndex,
    required this.question,
    required this.option,
  });
}

const List<QuestionModel> computerFundamentalsAndHtml = [
  QuestionModel(
    question:
        '1.MIME stands for -------------subject computer fundamentals and html',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    option: [
      'a) Multimedia Internet Mail Extensions',
      'b) Multipurpose Internet Multimedia Extensions',
      'c) Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions',
      'd) Multiple Internet Mail Extensions',
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
      question:
          '2. …………… attribute of a table determine how much space there is between the contents of a cell and its border.',
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
      option: [
        'a) cellspacing',
        'b) margin',
        'c) cellpadding',
        'd) cellborder',
      ]),
  QuestionModel(
    question: '3. ………………tag is used to include javascript into the HTML page.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    option: [
      'a) <link>',
      'b) <script>',
      'c) <javascript>',
      'd) <style>',
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    question: '4. In javascript what does is NaN function do?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    option: [
      'a) Return true if the argument is not a number ',
      'b) Return false if the argument is not a number',
      'c) Return true if the argument is a number ',
      'd) None of the above ',
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    question:
        '5. …………method is used to remove focus from the specified object.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    option: [
      'a) blur()',
      'b) unload()',
      'c) focus()',
      'd) removefocus()',
    ],
  ),
];

const List<QuestionModel> mathematicalFoundation = [
  QuestionModel(
    question: '1.MIME stands for--------------subject mathematical foundation ',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    option: [
      'a) Multimedia Internet Mail Extensions',
      'b) Multipurpose Internet Multimedia Extensions',
      'c) Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions',
      'd) Multiple Internet Mail Extensions',
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
      question:
          '2. …………… attribute of a table determine how much space there is between the contents of a cell and its border.',
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
      option: [
        'a) cellspacing',
        'b) margin',
        'c) cellpadding',
        'd) cellborder',
      ]),
  QuestionModel(
    question: '3. ………………tag is used to include javascript into the HTML page.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    option: [
      'a) <link>',
      'b) <script>',
      'c) <javascript>',
      'd) <style>',
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    question: '4. In javascript what does is NaN function do?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    option: [
      'a) Return true if the argument is not a number ',
      'b) Return false if the argument is not a number',
      'c) Return true if the argument is a number ',
      'd) None of the above ',
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    question:
        '5. …………method is used to remove focus from the specified object.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    option: [
      'a) blur()',
      'b) unload()',
      'c) focus()',
      'd) removefocus()',
    ],
  ),
];

const List<QuestionModel> discreteMathematics = [
  QuestionModel(
    question: '1.MIME stands for ---------------- subject discretemathematics',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    option: [
      'a) Multimedia Internet Mail Extensions',
      'b) Multipurpose Internet Multimedia Extensions',
      'c) Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions',
      'd) Multiple Internet Mail Extensions',
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
      question:
          '2. …………… attribute of a table determine how much space there is between the contents of a cell and its border.',
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
      option: [
        'a) cellspacing',
        'b) margin',
        'c) cellpadding',
        'd) cellborder',
      ]),
  QuestionModel(
    question: '3. ………………tag is used to include javascript into the HTML page.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    option: [
      'a) <link>',
      'b) <script>',
      'c) <javascript>',
      'd) <style>',
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    question: '4. In javascript what does is NaN function do?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    option: [
      'a) Return true if the argument is not a number ',
      'b) Return false if the argument is not a number',
      'c) Return true if the argument is a number ',
      'd) None of the above ',
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    question:
        '5. …………method is used to remove focus from the specified object.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    option: [
      'a) blur()',
      'b) unload()',
      'c) focus()',
      'd) removefocus()',
    ],
  ),
];
